<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The 5 Star Guide To Athens</string>

    <string name="name_attr_acropolis">Acropolis of Athens</string>
    <string name="address_attr_acropolis">Athens, 105 58</string>
    <string name="description_attr_acropolis">The Acropolis is the most important ancient site in
        the Western world. Crowned by the Parthenon, it stands sentinel over Athens, visible from
        almost everywhere within the city. Its monuments and sanctuaries of Pentelic marble gleam
        white in the midday sun and gradually take on a honey hue as the sun sinks, while at night
        they stand brilliantly illuminated above the city. A glimpse of this magnificent sight
        cannot fail to exalt your spirit. Inspiring as these monuments are, they are but faded
        remnants of the city of Pericles, who spared no expense – only the best materials,
        architects, sculptors and artists were good enough for a city dedicated to the cult of
        Athena. It was a showcase of lavishly coloured colossal buildings and of gargantuan statues,
        some of bronze, others of marble plated with gold and encrusted with precious stones. The
        Acropolis was first inhabited in Neolithic times (4000–3000 BC). The first temples were
        built during the Mycenaean era, in homage to the goddess Athena. People lived on the
        Acropolis until the late 6th century BC, but in 510 BC the Delphic oracle declared that it
        should be the province of the gods. After all the buildings on the Acropolis were reduced to
        ashes by the Persians on the eve of the Battle of Salamis (480 BC), Pericles set about his
        ambitious rebuilding program. He transformed the Acropolis into a city of temples, which has
        come to be regarded as the zenith of classical Greek achievement. Ravages inflicted during
        the years of foreign occupation, pilfering by foreign archaeologists, inept renovations
        following Independence, visitors’ footsteps, earthquakes and, more recently, acid rain and
        pollution have all taken their toll on the surviving monuments. The worst blow was in 1687,
        when the Venetians attacked the Turks, opening fire on the Acropolis and causing an
        explosion in the Parthenon – where the Turks had been storing gunpowder – and damaging all
        the buildings. Major restoration programs are continuing and many of the original sculptures
        have been moved to the Acropolis Museum and replaced with casts. The Acropolis became a
        World Heritage–listed site in 1987.</string>
    <string name="telephone_attr_acropolis">+30 21 0321 4172</string>
    <string name="url_attr_acropolis">odysseus.culture.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_attr_acropolis">37.971753, 23.725744</string>
    <string name="advice_attr_acropolis">Remember to bring a hat and water because
        the climb is difficult and the sun is hot</string>

    <string name="name_attr_ancientagora">Ancient Agora</string>
    <string name="address_attr_ancientagora">Adrianou, Athens, 105 55</string>
    <string name="description_attr_ancientagora">The heart of ancient Athens was the Agora, the
        lively, crowded focal point of administrative, commercial, political and social activity.
        Socrates expounded his philosophy here, and in AD 49 St Paul came here to win converts to
        Christianity. The site today is a lush, refreshing respite, with beautiful monuments and
        temples and a fascinating museum. First developed as a public site in the 6th century BC,
        the Agora was devastated by the Persians in 480 BC, but a new one was built in its place
        almost immediately. It was flourishing by Pericles’ time and continued to do so until
        AD 267, when it was destroyed by the Herulians, a Gothic tribe from Scandinavia. The Turks
        built a residential quarter on the site, but this was demolished by archaeologists after
        Independence and later excavated to classical and, in parts, Neolithic levels.</string>
    <string name="telephone_attr_ancientagora">+30 21 0321 0185</string>
    <string name="url_attr_ancientagora">odysseus.culture.gr/h/3/gh351.jsp?obj_id=2485</string>
    <string name="coordinates_attr_ancientagora">37.974658, 23.722002</string>
    <string name="advice_attr_ancientagora">After your visit you can have a coffee at the beautiful
        cafes at Adrianou street</string>

    <string name="name_attr_plaka">Plaka district</string>
    <string name="address_attr_plaka">Athens, 105 58</string>
    <string name="description_attr_plaka">Due to its proximity to the Acropolis, Plaka remains
        the area where the majority of foreign visitors stay and play. Its attractive features
        include small squares, some notable museums and the beautiful Mitropolis cathedral, as
        well as a host of places to stay, eat and drink. Its pedestrian zones make it a pleasant
        place to escape from the city’s notorious traffic. Adrianou and Kidathineon Streets
        contain a number of souvenir shops, offering classier items than you will find in the
        Flea Market. The most rewarding section to explore is the upper reaches towards the
        Acropolis itself, where many old stone houses with tiled roofs have survived. Up here
        you can find leafier corners and the odd quaint taverna with unobstructed views of the
        ancient rock.</string>
    <string name="telephone_attr_plaka" />
    <string name="url_attr_plaka" />
    <string name="coordinates_attr_plaka">37.971660, 23.730329</string>
    <string name="advice_attr_plaka">Don\'t miss the beautiful tavernas</string>

    <string name="name_attr_nam">National Archeological Museum</string>
    <string name="address_attr_nam">28 Oktovriou 44, Athens, 106 82</string>
    <string name="description_attr_nam">One of the world’s most important museums, the National
        Archaeological Museum houses the world\'s finest collection of Greek antiquities. Treasures
        offering a view of Greek art and history – dating from the Neolithic era to classical
        periods – include exquisite sculptures, pottery, jewellery, frescoes and artefacts found
        throughout Greece. The beautifully presented exhibits are displayed mainly thematically.
        Allow plenty of time to view the vast and spectacular collections (more than 11,000 items)
        housed in this enormous (8000-sq-metre) 19th-century neoclassical building. It could take
        several visits to appreciate the museum’s vast holdings, but it\'s possible to see the
        highlights in a half-day. The museum also hosts world-class temporary exhibitions. In
        addition to the highlights, the museum has a superb pottery collection on its upper floor,
        which traces the development of pottery from the Bronze Age through Attic red-figured
        pottery (late 5th to early 4th centuries BC). Among the treasures are six Panathenaic
        amphorae presented to the winners of the Panathenaic Games. They contained oil from the
        sacred olive trees of Athens and victors might have received up to 140 of them.</string>
    <string name="telephone_attr_nam">+30 21 3214 4800</string>
    <string name="url_attr_nam">www.namuseum.gr/wellcome-en.html</string>
    <string name="coordinates_attr_nam">37.989023, 23.732738</string>
    <string name="advice_attr_nam">Plan ahead and take your time. The museum is huge</string>

    <string name="name_attr_acropolismuseum">Acropolis Museum</string>
    <string name="address_attr_acropolismuseum">Dionysiou Areopagitou 15, Athens, 117 42</string>
    <string name="description_attr_acropolismuseum">This dazzling modernist museum at the foot of
        the Acropolis\' southern slope showcases its surviving treasures still in Greek possession.
        While the collection covers the Archaic and Roman periods, the emphasis is on the Acropolis
        of the 5th century BC, considered the apotheosis of Greece\'s artistic achievement. The
        museum cleverly reveals layers of history, floating over ruins with the Acropolis visible
        above, showing the masterpieces in context. The surprisingly good-value restaurant has
        superb views; there’s also a fine museum shop. Designed by US-based architect Bernard
        Tschumi with Greek architect Michael Photiadis, the €130-million museum includes items
        formerly held in other museums or in storage, as well as pieces returned from foreign
        museums. As you enter the museum grounds, look through the plexiglass floor to see the
        ruins of an ancient Athenian neighbourhood, which were artfully incorporated into the museum
        design after being uncovered during excavations. Finds from the slopes of the Acropolis are
        on display in the foyer gallery, which has an ascending glass floor emulating the climb up
        to the sacred hill, while allowing glimpses of the ruins below. Exhibits include painted
        vases and votive offerings from the sanctuaries where gods were worshipped, and more recent
        objects found in excavations of the settlement, including two clay statues of Nike at the
        entrance. Bathed in natural light, the 1st-floor Archaic Gallery is a veritable forest of
        statues, mostly votive offerings to Athena. These include stunning examples of 6th-century
        kore (maidens) – statues of young women in draped clothing and elaborate braids, usually
        carrying a pomegranate, wreath or bird. Most were recovered from a pit on the Acropolis,
        where the Athenians buried them after the Battle of Salamis. The 570 BC statue of a youth
        bearing a calf is one of the rare male statues found. There are also bronze figurines and
        artefacts from temples predating the Parthenon (destroyed by the Persians), including
        wonderful pedimental sculptures such as Hercules slaying the Lernaian Hydra and a lioness
        devouring a bull. Also on this floor are five Caryatids, the maiden columns that held up
        the Erechtheion (the sixth is in the British Museum), and a giant floral akrotirion (a
        decorative element capping a gable) that once crowned the southern ridge of the Parthenon
        pediment. The museum’s crowning glory is the top-floor Parthenon Gallery, a glass atrium
        built in alignment with the temple, and a virtual replica of the cella of the Parthenon,
        which can be seen from the gallery. It showcases the temple’s sculptures, metopes and 160m-
        long frieze, which for the first time in over 200 years is shown in sequence as one
        narrative about the Panathenaic Procession. The Procession starts at the southwest corner
        of the temple, with two groups splitting off and meeting on the east side for the delivery
        of the peplos to Athena. Interspersed between the golden-hued originals are stark-white
        plaster replicas of the missing pieces – the controversial Parthenon Marbles hacked off by
        Lord Elgin in 1801 and later sold to the British Museum (more than half the frieze is in
        London) – making a compelling case for their reunification.</string>
    <string name="telephone_attr_acropolismuseum">+30 21 0900 0900</string>
    <string name="url_attr_acropolismuseum">www.theacropolismuseum.gr/en</string>
    <string name="coordinates_attr_acropolismuseum">37.968458, 23.728566</string>
    <string name="advice_attr_acropolismuseum">Don’t miss the movie describing the history of the
        Acropolis.</string>

    <string name="name_attr_templeofolympianzeus">Temple of Olympian Zeus</string>
    <string name="address_attr_olympianzeus">Athens, 105 57</string>
    <string name="description_attr_templeofolympianzeus">You can’t miss this striking marvel smack
        in the centre of Athens. It is the largest temple in Greece; begun in the 6th century BC by
        Peisistratos, it was abandoned for lack of funds. Various other leaders had stabs at
        completing it, but it was left to Hadrian to complete the work in AD 131 – taking more than
        700 years in total to build. The temple is impressive for the sheer size of its 104
        Corinthian columns (17m high with a base diameter of 1.7m), of which 15 remain – the fallen
        column was blown down in a gale in 1852. Hadrian put a colossal statue of Zeus in the cella
        – and in typically immodest fashion, placed an equally large one of himself next to it.
    </string>
    <string name="telephone_attr_olympianzeus">+30 210 922 6330</string>
    <string name="url_attr_olympianzeus">odysseus.culture.gr/h/2/gh251.jsp?obj_id=12863</string>
    <string name="coordinates_attr_olympianzeus">37.969283, 23.733143</string>
    <string name="advice_attr_olympianzeus">You can get a multi-ticket that allows you to visit the
        Acropolis and 5 other sites</string>


    <string name="name_attr_lycabettus">Lycabettus Hill</string>
    <string name="address_attr_lycabettus">Athens, 114 71</string>
    <string name="description_attr_lycabettus">The name Lykavittos – ‘Hill of Wolves’ – derives from
        ancient times, when the hill was surrounded by countryside and its pine-covered slopes were
        inhabited by wolves. A path leads to the summit from the top of Loukianou for the finest
        panoramas of the city and the Attic basin – the nefos (pollution haze) permitting.
        Alternatively, take the funicular railway, or teleferik, from the top of Ploutarhou in
        Kolonaki. Perched on the summit is the little Chapel of Agios Giorgios, floodlit like a
        beacon over the city at night. Open-air Lykavittos Theatre, northeast of the summit, hosts
        concerts in summer.</string>
    <string name="telephone_attr_lycabettus" />
    <string name="url_attr_lycabettus" />
    <string name="coordinates_attr_lycabettus">37.982023, 23.743035</string>
    <string name="advice_attr_lycabettus">The view is magnificent</string>

    <string name="name_attr_panathenaicstadium">Panathenaic Stadium</string>
    <string name="address_attr_panathenaicstadium">Leoforos Vasileos Konstantinou, Athens, 116 35</string>
    <string name="description_panathenaicstadium">The grand Panathenaic Stadium lies between two
        pine-covered hills between the neighbourhoods of Mets and Pangrati. It was originally built
        in the 4th century BC as a venue for the Panathenaic athletic contests. It\'s said that at
        Hadrian’s inauguration in AD 120, 1000 wild animals were sacrificed in the arena. Later, the
        seats were rebuilt in Pentelic marble by Herodes Atticus. There are seats for 70,000
        spectators, a running track and a central area for field events. After hundreds of years of
        disuse, the stadium was completely restored in 1895 by wealthy Greek benefactor Georgios
        Averof to host the first modern Olympic Games the following year. It\'s a faithful replica
        of the original Panathenaic Stadium, and it made a stunning backdrop to the archery
        competition and the marathon finish during the 2004 Olympics. It\'s occasionally used for
        concerts and public events, and the annual Athens marathon finishes here.</string>
    <string name="telephone_attr_panathenaicstadium">+30 21 0752 2984</string>
    <string name="url_attr_panathenaicstadium">www.panathenaicstadium.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_attr_panathenaicstadium">37.968334, 23.741101</string>
    <string name="advice_attr_panathenaicstadium">The first modern Olympic games were hosted here in
        1896</string>

    <string name="name_attr_unknownsoldier">Tomb of the Unknown Soldier</string>
    <string name="address_attr_unknownsoldier">Leoforos Vasilissis Amalias 133, Athens, 105 57</string>
    <string name="description_attr_tomboftheunknownsoldier">In front of the parliament building on
        Plateia Syntagmatos, the traditionally costumed evzones (guards) of the Tomb of the Unknown
        Soldier change every hour on the hour. On Sunday at 11am, a whole platoon marches down
        Vasilissis Sofias to the tomb, accompanied by a band. The presidential guards\' uniform of
        short kilts and pom-pom shoes is based on the attire worn by the klephts (the mountain
        fighters of the War of Independence).</string>
    <string name="telephone_attr_unknownsoldier" />
    <string name="coordinates_attr_unknownsoldier">37.975350, 23.736366</string>
    <string name="url_attr_unknownsoldier" />
    <string name="advice_attr_unknownsoldier">The guards are very impressive standing absolutely
        still no matter the conditions</string>

    <string name="name_attr_benaki">Benaki Museum</string>
    <string name="address_attr_benaki">Koumbari 1, Athens, 106 74</string>
    <string name="description_attr_benaki">Greece’s finest private museum contains the vast
        collection of Antonis Benakis, accumulated during 35 years of avid collecting in Europe and
        Asia. The collection includes Bronze Age finds from Mycenae and Thessaly; works by El Greco;
        ecclesiastical furniture brought from Asia Minor; pottery, copper, silver and woodwork from
        Egypt, Asia Minor and Mesopotamia; and a stunning collection of Greek regional costumes. The
        museum has expanded into several branches, including the Pireos Annexe, to house its vast
        and diverse collections and is a major player in the city’s arts scene. It hosts a full
        schedule of rotating exhibitions.</string>
    <string name="telephone_attr_benaki">+30 21 0367 1000</string>
    <string name="url_attr_benaki">www.benaki.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_attr_benaki">37.975944, 23.740457</string>
    <string name="advice_attr_benaki">The museum store has excellent gift ideas and the restaurant
        at the top floor is worth a visit</string>

    <string name="name_attr_cycladic">Museum of Cycladic Art</string>
    <string name="address_attr_cycladic">Neofytou Douka 4, Athens, 106 74</string>
    <string name="description_attr_cycladicart">This exceptional private museum boasts the largest
        independent collection of distinctive Cycladic art and holds excellent periodic exhibitions
        of all sorts. The 1st-floor Cycladic collection, dating from 3000 BC to 2000 BC, includes
        the marble figurines that inspired many 20th-century artists, such as Picasso and Modigliani,
        with their simplicity and purity of form. The rest of the museum features Greek and Cypriot
        art dating from 2000 BC to the 4th century AD. The 4th-floor exhibition, Scenes from Daily
        Life in Antiquity, includes artefacts and films depicting life in Ancient Greece.</string>
    <string name="telephone_attr_cycladic">+30 21 0722 8321</string>
    <string name="url_attr_cycladic">www.cycladic.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_attr_cycladic">37.975703, 23.742211</string>
    <string name="advice_attr_cycladic">Start your visit from the 4th floor and then descent</string>


    <string name="name_attr_byzantine"><![CDATA[Byzantine & Christian Museum]]></string>
    <string name="address_attr_byzantine">Leoforos Vasilissis Sofias 22, Athens, 106 75</string>
    <string name="description_attr_byzantinemuseum">This outstanding museum – on the grounds of
        former Villa Ilissia, an urban oasis – presents a priceless collection of Christian art from
        the 3rd to 20th centuries. Thematic snapshots of the Byzantine and post-Byzantine world are
        exceptionally presented in expansive, well-lit, multilevel galleries, clearly arranged
        chronologically with English translations. The collection includes icons, frescoes,
        sculptures, textiles, manuscripts, vestments and mosaics. The villa grounds, which sit next
        to Aristotle’s Lyceum, include ancient ruins such as the Peisistratos aqueduct.</string>
    <string name="telephone_attr_byzantine">+30 21 0723 1570</string>
    <string name="url_attr_byzantine">www.byzantinemuseum.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_attr_byzantine">37.975418, 23.744582</string>
    <string name="advice_attr_byzantine">You can combine your visit to the Byzantine museum with the
        Benaki and the Cycladic art museums as they are really close one to the other</string>

    <string name="name_hot_grandebretagne">Grande Bretagne</string>
    <string name="address_hot_grandebretagne">Vasileos Georgiou A’ 1, 105 64, Athens</string>
    <string name="description_hot_grandebretagne">If you aspire to the best, the place to stay in
        Athens is – and always has been – the Grande Bretagne, right on the Syntagma square. Built
        in 1862 to accommodate visiting heads of state, it ranks among the grandest hotels in the
        world. Though renovated some years ago, it still retains its old-world grandeur. There is a
        divine spa, and the Acropolis-view rooftop restaurant and bar are worth a visit, even if you
        aren’t a guest.</string>
    <string name="telephone_hot_grandebretagne">+30 210 3330000</string>
    <string name="url_hot_grandebretagne">grandebretagne.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_hot_grandebretagne">37.976338, 23.735339</string>
    <string name="advice_hot_grandebretagne">The atmosphere during the Christmas holidays is
        extravagant</string>

    <string name="name_hot_cocomat">COCO-MAT Hotel Athens</string>
    <string name="address_hot_cocomat">Patriarchou Ioakeim 36, Athens, 106 75 </string>
    <string name="telephone_hot_cocomat">+30 21 0723 0000</string>
    <string name="description_hot_cocomat">COCO-MAT is a greek producer of quality mattresses and
        pillows. You can rest reassured that you will sleep like a baby! COCO-MAT Hotel Athens is an
        understated luxury, design hotel that sits in the heart of Kolonaki, perhaps the city’s most
        exclusive district, and offers relaxing sleep, delicious homemade breakfast and selected
        services for its esteemed guests.</string>
    <string name="url_hot_cocomat">www.cocomatathens.com/</string>
    <string name="coordinates_hot_cocomat">37.977950, 23.744173</string>
    <string name="advice_hot_cocomat">Homemade breakfast buffet available from 7 to 11. Takeaway
        meals and beach towels available.</string>

    <string name="name_hot_hilton">Hilton Athens</string>
    <string name="address_hot_hilton">Vasilissis Sofias 46, Athens, 115 28</string>
    <string name="telephone_hot_hilton">+30 21 0728 1000</string>
    <string name="description_hot_hilton">Located in the heart of Athens, the Hilton Athens boasts
        elegant rooms, 3 swimming pools, the popular rooftop Galaxy Bar and 4 restaurants.
        Evangelismos Metro Station is just a few steps away and connects to Syntagma Square within
        5 minutes. This 5-star hotel offers spacious rooms and suites with marble bathrooms with
        walk-in shower and bathtub. LCD TVs with cable and satellite channels, and work desks with
        adjustable lamps are included. Floor-to-ceiling patio doors and balconies offer views of the
        Athenian landscape or the Acropolis. Milos Restaurant, which serves Greek gourmet cuisine
        including fresh fish is a favourite of local celebrities. The Byzantino restaurant proposes
        a Mediterranean buffet or a la carte menu and the richest Sunday brunch in Athens. On the
        11th floor, guests can access the Executive Lounge offering free breakfast and refreshments
        to Executive rooms residents. The stylish rooftop Galaxy Bar serves signature cocktails,
        whilst offering Acropolis views from its open-air terrace. The Oasis Pool Bar &amp; Grill
        serves Mediterranean cuisine or snacks. Located in the commercial district of the city, the
        hotel is just 500 m from the National Art Gallery, the Athens Concert Hall and the Kolonaki
        shopping district. The famous Acropolis of Athens is 4 km away and the historic Plaka area
        lies within 2.5 km. </string>
    <string name="url_hot_hilton">www3.hilton.com/en/hotels/greece/hilton-athens-ATHHITW/index.html</string>
    <string name="coordinates_hot_hilton">37.976475, 23.750417</string>
    <string name="advice_hot_hilton">Especially for the kids, hilton offers a huge swimming pool and
        a creative playing area next to the main restaurant</string>

    <string name="name_hot_electrametropolis">Electra Metropolis Athens</string>
    <string name="address_hot_electrametropolis">Mitropoleos 15, Athens, 105 57</string>
    <string name="telephone_hot_electrametropolis">+30 21 4100 6200</string>
    <string name="description_hot_electrametropolis">The latest addition of the Electra Hotels
        family, the Electra Metropolis Athens hotel, adds an aura of luxury to the city of Athens.
        A unique sky-lit atrium along with a modern interior design allow guests to enjoy a hotel
        experience in classic atmosphere while exploring the historical landmarks of the Greek
        capital. All rooms and suites of the Electra Metropolis hotel are modernly equipped with all
        the necessary amenities, while the wooden floors and the warm colors set the tone for
        relaxation. Furthermore, the suites of this luxurious city hotel offer spectacular views to
        Lycabettus Hill and the Acropolis. Equipped with modern facilities, the “Metropolis Roof
        Garden” and the “M bar” both located on the 10th floor, the Electra Metropolis hotel
        constitutes the ideal setting to indulge yourself in modern luxury in the heart of the
        city.</string>
    <string name="url_hot_electrametropolis">www.electrahotels.gr/</string>
    <string name="coordinates_hot_electrametropolis">37.975128, 23.732162</string>
    <string name="advice_hot_electrametropolis">The bar-restaurant on the last floor has a striking
        view to the Acropolis</string>

    <string name="name_hot_inn">in[n]Athens Urban Stay</string>
    <string name="address_hot_inn">Georgiou Souri 3, Athens, 105 57</string>
    <string name="telephone_hot_inn">+30 210 3258555</string>
    <string name="description_hot_inn">InnAthens Hotel have managed to bring together comfort and
        modern design in the perfect location. Right in the center of Athens, just a few steps from
        Syntagma square, the never sleeping Ermou str. and the breathtaking Acropolis InnAthens have
        established the ideal urban destination. With just 20 rooms in total, InnAthens\' goal is
        for the guests to enjoy a personalized experience, reminiscent of the vintage yet
        industrialized city of Athens. Greek marble and steel come together harmonically and bring
        out the Greek chic character of the rooms and the lobby area. Each room is unique and all
        elements are handpicked and custom made. The hotel\'s philosophy is for the  visitors to feel
        comfortable and at home in such a way that their stay in our hotel will be part of a unique
        experience of their trip in Athens.</string>
    <string name="url_hot_inn">www.innathens.com</string>
    <string name="coordinates_hot_inn">37.973479, 23.734347</string>
    <string name="advice_hot_inn">The hotel offers take-away breakfast if you check-out early</string>

    <string name="name_hot_astir">Astir Palace</string>
    <string name="address_hot_astir">Apollonos 40, Vouliagmeni, 166 71</string>
    <string name="telephone_hot_astir">+30 21 0890 2000</string>
    <string name="description_hot_astir">The world-renowned Astir Palace is a luxury resort on the
        Athenian Riviera, consisting of the five-star hotels, Arion, a Luxury Collection Resort
        &amp; Spa and The Westin Athens. Sprawling across 75 acres of sun-drenched gardens on a
        pine-dotted private peninsula, the resort complex boasts breathtaking views of the Saronic
        Gulf on the Mediterranean Sea and three private beaches including Astir beach and Astir
        Marina. </string>
    <string name="url_hot_astir">www.astirpalace.com</string>
    <string name="coordinates_hot_astir">37.804613, 23.771293</string>
    <string name="advice_hot_astir">Currently the hotel is being fully renovated and will be closed
        for the summer of 2017</string>

    <string name="name_hot_margi">The Margi</string>
    <string name="address_hot_margi">Litous 11, Vouliagmeni, 166 71</string>
    <string name="telephone_hot_margi">+30 21 0892 9000</string>
    <string name="description_hot_margi">The most hospitable, elegant and arty hotel of the Athenian
        Riviera is recommended for brief escapes with a taste of the tropics, for magical evenings
        by the pool and for candle-lit romantic dinners. In the early 60s, when influential Greeks
        decided to transform a part of the Saronic coast into a chic and glamorous holiday
        destination, to create their very own Côte d’ Azur a doctor, Yancos Stavridis, shared his
        vision of an Athenian Riviera and contributed by founding The Margi Hotel. Now, several
        decades later, its boutique esthetic, its warm luxury and its Mediterranean vibe, have
        helped The Margi emerge as one of Athens’ favorite hotels. Small objets d’art, ethnic
        details and design references complete its mystical setting. It is located near Athens’ most
        elegant sandy beach and yacht marina in Vouliagmeni on the southern coast, offering guests
        the chance to enjoy the Greek summer and all that it entails: diving in the waters of
        Vouliagmeni Bay, taking day-cruises, enjoying the sea breeze and exploring cosmopolital
        Glyfada – just five minutes away – for shopping and fun. At the end of the day, returning to
        this warm and luxurious haven is ample reward.</string>
    <string name="url_hot_margi">www.themargi.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_hot_margi">37.813884, 23.774010</string>
    <string name="advice_hot_margi">Patio restaurant has been named by CNN as one of the best new
        restaurants in the world for 2017</string>

    <string name="name_hot_periscope">Periscope</string>
    <string name="address_hot_periscope">Haritos 22, Athens, 106 75</string>
    <string name="telephone_hot_periscope">+30 21 0729 7200</string>
    <string name="description_hot_periscope">Right in chic Kolonaki overlooking Lykavittos,
        Periscope is a design hotel with industrial decor. Clever gadgets are sprinkled throughout,
        including the lobby slide show and aerial shots of the city on the ceilings. Korres organic
        toiletries and the trendy Pbox restaurant add to the vibe. The penthouse’s private rooftop
        spa has sensational views.Boasting a central location, in the heart of Kolonaki, Periscope
        is a boutique city hotel offering minimally decorated accommodation with state-of-the-art
        facilities. Periscope rooms and suites are soundproofed with wooden floors. Each comes with
        a flat-screen TV, CD and DVD library, and pillow menu. The modern bathrooms are stocked with
        luxurious toiletries, bathrobes and slippers.</string>
    <string name="url_hot_periscope">www.yeshotels.gr/hotel/periscope</string>
    <string name="coordinates_hot_periscope">37.978322, 23.744074</string>
    <string name="advice_hot_periscope">Haritos street is a very vivid one (full of bars and
        restaurants) so if you like quiet choose a high floor room</string>

    <string name="name_hot_360">360 Degrees</string>
    <string name="address_hot_360">Plateia Monastirakiou, Athens, 105 55</string>
    <string name="telephone_hot_360">+30 21 0324 0034</string>
    <string name="description_hot_360">Smack on Monastiraki square, these modern rooms are topped by
        a super roof restaurant serving up those eponymous 360-degree views. For the quietest rooms,
        book on an upper floor, facing away from the square.</string>
    <string name="url_hot_360">www.360hotelathens.com</string>
    <string name="coordinates_hot_360">37.976421, 23.725669</string>
    <string name="advice_hot_360">Avoid the rooms in the front, Monastiraki square can be quite
        noisy. Apart from this, the location is superb</string>

    <string name="name_hot_new">New Hotel</string>
    <string name="address_hot_new">Filellinon 16, Athens, 105 57</string>
    <string name="telephone_hot_new">+30 21 0327 3000</string>
    <string name="description_hot_new">Whether you dig the groovy, top-designer Campana Brothers
        furniture or the sleeping-pillow menu (tell ’em how you like it!), you’ll find some sort of
        decadent treat here to tickle your fancy. Part of a renowned local design-hotel group, NEW
        Hotel is the latest entry on the high-end Athens scene. This brand new design hotel stands
        in a prominent central city location, 200 metres from Syntagma Square. With free Wi-Fi
        throughout the property, New Hotel houses a Mediterranean restaurant and a fitness area.
        Designed by award-winning Brazilian designers the Campana Brothers, 79-room and non-smoking
        New Hotel is a member of Design Hotels of the world. The New Hotel was formerly the Olympic
        Palace Hotel and while strikingly modern in design today, original features have been
        retained, including the 1940s black marble staircase. Rooms feature floor to ceiling
        windows, bamboo floors and tables.The impressive bathrooms have solid brass washbasins.
        LCD TVs are standard.</string>
    <string name="url_hot_new">www.yeshotels.gr/hotel/new-hotel</string>
    <string name="coordinates_hot_new">37.973338, 23.733639</string>
    <string name="advice_hot_new">One of the best Sunday brunches in town</string>

    <string name="name_din_cookoovaya">Cookoovaya</string>
    <string name="address_din_cookoovaya">Chatzigianni Mexi 2A, 115 28, Athens</string>
    <string name="description_din_cookoovaya">Greek cuisine, developed though life experiences,
        inspiration and ingredients entrusted to their capable hands, complements your group,
        whether a party of two, three or many more.</string>
    <string name="telephone_din_cookoovaya">+30 210 7235 005</string>
    <string name="url_din_cookoovaya">cookoovaya.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_din_cookoovaya">37.977021, 23.751437</string>
    <string name="advice_din_cookoovaya">Five chefs have joined forces and the result is amazing</string>

    <string name="name_din_dionysos">Dionysos</string>
    <string name="address_din_dionysos">Rovertou Galli 43, Athens, 117 43</string>
    <string name="description_din_dionysos">Location, location, location. Eat here for the fantastic
        sweep of plate glass looking out onto the unblemished south slope of the Acropolis. Food is
        pricey but service is attentive… Date night?</string>
    <string name="telephone_din_dionysos">+30 21 0923 3182</string>
    <string name="url_din_dionysos">www.dionysoszonars.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_din_dionysos">37.969483, 23.722448</string>
    <string name="advice_din_dionysos">Dionysos restaurant is frequently used to host foreign
        leaders on their visit in Greece</string>

    <string name="name_din_varoulko">Varoulko</string>
    <string name="address_din_varoulko">Akti Koumoundourou 52, Pireus, 104 35</string>
    <string name="description_din_varoulko">For a heady Greek dining experience, try the
        Michelin-starred combination of waterfront views and Lefteris Lazarou\'s delicious seafood.
        Sip on top wines as sailboats bob in the harbour at Mikrolimano.</string>
    <string name="telephone_din_varoulko">+30 21 0522 8400</string>
    <string name="url_din_varoulko">www.varoulko.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_din_varoulko">37.937403, 23.658438</string>
    <string name="advice_din_varoulko">Chef Lefteris Lazarou was a judge on the greek version of
        Master Chef</string>

    <string name="name_din_basegrill">Basegrill</string>
    <string name="address_din_basegrill">Leoforos Konstantinoupoleos 64, Peristeri, 121 33</string>
    <string name="description_din_basegrill">There’s no need to reiterate that this restaurant
        serves what are perhaps the finest Greek steak along with the most celebrated “eggs and
        fries” in the entire country. After all, the restaurant\'s motto is "Only our salt comes
        from the sea". </string>
    <string name="telephone_din_basegrill">+30 21 0575 7455</string>
    <string name="url_din_basegrill">www.basegrillathens.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_din_basegrill">38.011887, 23.708182</string>
    <string name="advice_din_basegrill">Book ahead, the place can get crowded</string>

    <string name="name_din_kuzina">Kuzina</string>
    <string name="address_din_kuzina">Adrianou 9, Athens, 105 55</string>
    <string name="description_din_kuzina">Light streams through plate-glass windows, warming the
        crowded tables in winter. Or eat outside on pedestrianised, people-watching Adrianou in
        summer. Expect inventive Greek fusion, such as Cretan pappardelle or chicken with figs and
        sesame.</string>
    <string name="telephone_din_kuzina">+30 21 0324 0133</string>
    <string name="url_din_kuzina">www.kuzina.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_din_kuzina">37.976415, 23.722034</string>
    <string name="advice_din_kuzina">The view of the Acropolis from the terrace is magnificent</string>

    <string name="name_din_yolenis">Yoleni\'s</string>
    <string name="address_din_yolenis">Solonos 9, Athens, 106 71</string>
    <string name="description_din_yolenis">Organic extra-virgin olive oil, wild herbs, cheeses from
        around Greece, Cretan honey, truffle salt. Artisanal breadsticks and ‘spoon’ sweets.
        Selected wines and pasta. All those things that are sometimes hard to find, even if you live
        in Greece, are now only a few clicks away.</string>
    <string name="telephone_din_yolenis">+30 21 2222 3622</string>
    <string name="url_din_yolenis">www.yolenis.com</string>
    <string name="coordinates_din_yolenis">37.977668, 23.738824</string>
    <string name="advice_din_yolenis">Apart from the restaurant there is a grocery store with greek
        products in the basement and a children\'s play area on the second floor</string>

    <string name="name_din_parkoeleftherias">To Parko Eleftherias</string>
    <string name="address_din_parkoeleftherias">Park Eleftherias Vasilisis Sofias, Athens, 115 21</string>
    <string name="description_din_parkoeleftherias">With low-key music and a romantic setting, Parko
        is located in the greenery next to the Megaron Mousikis concert hall (and the U.S. Embassy)
        and is a summer favorite for snacks, food and drink, day and night.</string>
    <string name="telephone_din_parkoeleftherias">+30 21 0722 3784</string>
    <string name="url_din_parkoeleftherias">www.toparko.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_din_parkoeleftherias">37.980106, 23.751943</string>
    <string name="advice_din_parkoeleftherias">You won\'t believe there is such a beautiful garden
        in the heart of the city. The menu comprises of typical greek plates.</string>

    <string name="name_din_spondi">Spondi</string>
    <string name="address_din_spondi">Pyrronos 5, Athens, 116 36</string>
    <string name="description_din_spondi">Two Michelin–starred Spondi is frequently voted Athens’
        best restaurant, and the accolades are deserved. It offers Mediterranean haute cuisine, with
        heavy French influences, in a relaxed, chic setting in a charming old house. Choose from the
        menu or a range of set dinner and wine prix fixes. The restaurant has a lovely,
        bougainvillea-draped garden.</string>
    <string name="telephone_din_spondi">+30 21 0752 0658</string>
    <string name="url_din_spondi">www.spondi.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_din_spondi">37.965153, 23.743050</string>
    <string name="advice_din_spondi">If you like gourmet dinning, Spondi is considered to be the
        best greek restaurant</string>

    <string name="name_din_matsuhisa">Matsuhisa Athens</string>
    <string name="address_din_matsuhisa">Apollonos 40, Vouliagmeni, 166 71</string>
    <string name="description_din_matsuhisa">Come to Greece to eat sushi? Well why not, if you\'re
        in the mood to hang with chic Athenians at this popular waterfront restaurant that\'s run by
        world-famous restaurateur Nobu Matsuhisa. Views are exquisite – to match the people and the
        pricetag. Book ahead.</string>
    <string name="telephone_din_matsuhisa">matsuhisaathens.com</string>
    <string name="url_din_matsuhisa">www.matsuhisaathens.com</string>
    <string name="coordinates_din_matsuhisa">37.806999, 23.772193</string>
    <string name="advice_din_matsuhisa">Combine your visit with the next-door Astir
        private beach club for a perfect seaside experience.</string>

    <string name="name_din_zonars">Zonar\'s</string>
    <string name="address_din_zonars">Voukourestiou 9, Athens, 106 71</string>
    <string name="description_din_zonars">Zonar\'s is the most historic coffee-pastry shop in
        Athens. Today, Zonar\'s maintains its secular character, serves fresh ideas, while it still
        maintains the traditional style. The place is elegant with art deco elements.</string>
    <string name="telephone_din_zonars">+30 21 0325 1430</string>
    <string name="url_din_zonars">www.zonarsathens.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_din_zonars">37.977308, 23.735273</string>
    <string name="advice_din_zonars">The most expensive coffee in town, but still worth the
        experience</string>

    <string name="name_sho_goldenhall">Golden Hall</string>
    <string name="address_sho_goldenhall">Leoforos Kifisias 37A, Marousi, 151 23</string>
    <string name="description_sho_goldenhall">At an excellent and the same time easily accessible
        location, at Kifissias avenue, at Maroussi, Golden Hall has been created for the visitor who
        wants the best in shopping. It has been awarded as the best shopping centre in Europe and at
        its 41,000m2 you will find 131 stores with brands, elegant restaurants and cafes, an
        outdoors area next to the entrance so you can enjoy the sun, but also the various events
        that are organized and an underground two-level parking space with 1,400 available
        spots.</string>
    <string name="telephone_sho_goldenhall">+30 21 0680 3450</string>
    <string name="url_sho_goldenhall">www.goldenhall.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_sho_goldenhall">38.034123, 23.792276</string>
    <string name="advice_sho_goldenhall">Combine shopping with kids activities (indoor and outdoor
        playgrounds, Lego area etc)</string>

    <string name="name_sho_id">i-D Concept Store</string>
    <string name="address_sho_id">Kanari 12, 106 74, Athens</string>
    <string name="description_sho_id">“i-D Concept Stores” aims to offer you a unique collection of
        hand-picked jewelry, colorful accessories, eclectic apparel and unique objects.  i-D’s
        flagship store spans 3500 square feet of retail space in the urban chic Kolonaki center of
        Athens and comprises three floors of stylish, elegant, sophisticated, contemporary and edgy
        men’s and women’s collections, a dedicated art area and a special place for unique designer
        exhibits.</string>
    <string name="telephone_sho_id">+30 210 3221801</string>
    <string name="url_sho_id">www.idconceptstores.com</string>
    <string name="coordinates_sho_id">37.977008, 23.739400</string>
    <string name="advice_sho_id">Check out Wings and Kooreloo handcrafted handbags</string>

    <string name="name_sho_attica">attica, The Department Store</string>
    <string name="address_sho_attica">Panepistimiou 9, Athens, 105 64</string>
    <string name="description_sho_attica">This upmarket department store in the Citylink complex
        (which houses top fashion labels and jewellers) has eight levels crammed with leading
        brands, hip clothing, cosmetics and designer temptations.</string>
    <string name="telephone_sho_attica">+30 21 1180 2600</string>
    <string name="url_sho_attica">www.atticadps.gr/</string>
    <string name="coordinates_sho_attica">37.977606, 23.734969</string>
    <string name="advice_sho_attica">Don\'t miss a passage called stoa Milliou behind attica, which
        houses some very nice cafe-restaurants</string>

    <string name="name_sho_ileanamakri">Ileana Makri</string>
    <string name="address_sho_ileanamakri">Haritos 11A, Athens, 106 75</string>
    <string name="description_sho_ileanamakri">Barneys New York was the first store to stock Greek
        designer Ileana Makri’s collection of evil eyes and Fatima hands back in 1999, but now
        boutiques and luxe department shops around the globe feature Makri’s pieces. The designer\'s
        concept store in Kolonaki is a bazaar of carefully curated designer jewelry and fashion,
        as well as a showroom for gorgeous, gem-encrusted pieces that sit beautifully in glass
        cases.</string>
    <string name="telephone_sho_ileanamakri">+30 21 0725 1471</string>
    <string name="url_sho_ileanamakri">www.ileanamakri.com</string>
    <string name="coordinates_sho_ileanamakri">37.978162, 23.743049</string>
    <string name="advice_sho_ileanamakri">Don\'t miss the collection of "evil eyes"</string>

    <string name="name_sho_thalassa">Thalassa Collection</string>
    <string name="address_sho_thalassa">Patriarchou Ioakeim 30–32, Athens, 106 75</string>
    <string name="description_sho_thalassa">Thalassa Collection is located in the fashionable
        Kolonaki district and specializes in the design and production of scarves, ties, shawls.
        Mainly inspired by Greek tradition and history, all patterns are exclusively designed in the
        Athens atelier and printed on fine quality fabrics such as silk, cashmere, cotton. Some of
        the best selling designs are the "Greek Alphabet" design, the "Evil Eye", the "Tsarouhi",
        and also the designs inspired from the Greek Islands. The obsession in every single detail,
        the use of fine quality materials, and the incredibly rich variety of colors are the key
        element that define the world of Thalassa Collection.</string>
    <string name="telephone_sho_thalassa">+30 21 0725 8525</string>
    <string name="url_sho_thalassa">www.thalassacollection.com/</string>
    <string name="coordinates_sho_thalassa">37.977945, 23.743932</string>
    <string name="advice_sho_thalassa">Thalassa recently opened a second store in Valoritou street</string>

    <string name="name_sho_apivita">The Apivita Experience Store</string>
    <string name="address_sho_apivita">Solonos 6, Athens, 106 73</string>
    <string name="description_sho_apivita">This five-storey beauty emporium and spa stocks Apivita’s
        chemical-free cosmetics made with honey, royal jelly and bee pollen. You can create your own
        personalized beauty products with a pharmacist and aromatherapist. At the cozy, top-floor
        Beehive spa, the cabins are made of beehives and the ceiling is honey-tinted crystal.</string>
    <string name="telephone_sho_apivita">+30 21 0364 0560</string>
    <string name="url_sho_apivita">www.apivita.com</string>
    <string name="coordinates_sho_apivita">37.977362, 23.739289</string>
    <string name="advice_sho_apivita">On the 1st floor you can find a nice bio-juice bar. Also, here
        you can find excellent honey.</string>

    <string name="name_sho_monastiraki">Monastiraki Flea market</string>
    <string name="address_sho_monastiraki">Ifaistou, Athens, 105 55</string>
    <string name="description_sho_monastiraki">This traditional market has a festive atmosphere,
        combined with an onslaught of more modern souvenir stalls. Permanent antique and
        collectables shops are open all week, while the streets around the station and Adrianou fill
        with vendors selling jewellery, handicrafts and bric-a-brac.</string>
    <string name="telephone_sho_monastiraki">+30 694 608 6114</string>
    <string name="url_sho_monastiraki"></string>
    <string name="coordinates_sho_monastiraki">37.976611, 23.723896</string>
    <string name="advice_sho_monastiraki">Don\'t forget to barter, it\'s part of the process</string>

    <string name="name_sho_ermou">Ermou street</string>
    <string name="address_sho_ermou">Ermou, Athens, 105 57</string>
    <string name="description_sho_ermou">If you start at the top of Syntagma Square and walk down
        the steps and past the fountain, at the bottom of the square is the beginning of Ermou
        Street, a paradise for those who live to shop. From the Parliament building you can make a
        straight line that follows Ermou all the way to The Gazi, the old gas works of Athens. Ermou
        street is a commercial avenue which has been turned into a pedestrian only street . It is
        the primary clothing shopping street for Athens and contains many of the big international
        names.</string>
    <string name="telephone_sho_ermou"></string>
    <string name="url_sho_ermou"></string>
    <string name="coordinates_sho_ermou">37.975688, 23.733691</string>
    <string name="advice_sho_ermou">If you are looking for children\'s clothing don\'t miss Lapin
        House</string>

    <string name="name_kid_snfcc">Stavros Niarchos Foundation Cultural Center</string>
    <string name="address_kid_snfcc">Andrea Syngrou 364, 176 74, Kallithea</string>
    <string name="description_kid_snfcc">The Stavros Niarchos Foundation Cultural
        Center is a complex in the bay of Phaliron in Athens which includes new
        facilities for the National Library of Greece and the National Opera. The
        Center was designed by architect Renzo Piano and is being built by the
        Stavros Niarchos Foundation. The €566 million project was completed in
        2016, and was donated to the Greek state in 2017.</string>
    <string name="telephone_kid_snfcc">+30 21 6809 1000</string>
    <string name="url_kid_snfcc">snfcc.org</string>
    <string name="coordinates_kid_snfcc">37.939984, 23.691899</string>
    <string name="advice_kid_snfcc">Plenty of activities for the young ones, including a music
        playground and kids library</string>

    <string name="name_kid_nationalgarden">National Garden</string>
    <string name="address_kid_nationalgarden">Amalias 1, Athens, 105 57</string>
    <string name="description_kid_nationalgarden">Just a few metres away from Syntagma metro station
        and right next to the Greek parliament lies the national garden which, together with the
        zappeion hall garden, covers 24 hectares full of vegetation, rare kinds of plants, saplings
        and birds.</string>
    <string name="telephone_kid_nationalgarden">+30 21 0721 5019</string>
    <string name="url_kid_nationalgarden">www.cityofathens.gr/node/614</string>
    <string name="coordinates_kid_nationalgarden">37.973441, 23.737855</string>
    <string name="advice_kid_nationalgarden">During June 2017, the city of Athens is organizing more
        than 150 activities in the garden</string>

    <string name="name_kid_childrensmuseum">Hellenic Children\'s Museum</string>
    <string name="address_kid_childrensmuseum"><![CDATA[Rigillis & Vasileos Georgiou B\' 17–19,
    Athens, 106 75]]></string>
    <string name="description_kid_childrensmuseum">The Hellenic Children\'s Museum has a variety of
        exhibits that aim to help every child understand the world in which he or she lives, in his
        or her own way. The philosophy of the Hellenic Children’s Museum is based on the phrase “I
        hear and I forget, I see and I remember, I do and I understand”. In the Children’s Museum,
        children can broaden their knowledge and experiences in many different areas. The exhibit
        Hello Pythagoras helps children understand the concept of geometry. In the Playground, they
        play with building materials to create different constructions. At the Marketplace, they are
        taught about the concept of supply and demand, and in the Kitchen area, they experiment with
        food ingredients and recipes and have the opportunity to try their hand at cooking. While
        the programmes are in Greek, they can also be conducted in English upon special request. The
        museum organises recreational activities depending on children’s ages as well as seasonal
        educational programmes. It is worth visiting the toy store with its innovative games that
        stir children’s imagination and the materials store that has cheap recycled materials with
        which children can build creative constructions and get acquainted with the concept of
        recycling.</string>
    <string name="telephone_kid_childrensmuseum">+30 21 0331 2995</string>
    <string name="url_kid_childrensmuseum">www.hcm.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_kid_childrensmuseum">37.973480, 23.744220</string>
    <string name="advice_kid_childrensmuseum">Although it is called a museum it is actually a very
        nice playground for the liitle ones</string>

    <string name="name_kid_alloufunpark">Allou! Fun Park</string>
    <string name="address_kid_alloufunpark">Leoforos Kifissou &amp; Petrou Ralli, Agios Ioannis
        Rentis, 182 33</string>
    <string name="description_kid_alloufunpark">Allou ! Fun Park in the neighborhood of Rentis, is
        one of the most popular destinations for kids and adults, offering a wide choice of
        entertainment and fun. An impressive choice of games for all preferences attract crowds
        specially on weekends, who enjoy the excitement. Four dimension experiences at the 4D Gate,
        crazy rotations at Crazy Mouse and Big Apple, rafting at La Isla and many more rides and
        games for unforgettable moments. At Kidom, the park only for kids, a series of unique games
        keep children happy, like the Carousel, the Bongo flying elephants, trains, the Youpi Tower,
        Bloom Bloom boats and the mega colorful inflatable toys. Happenings, events and concerts are
        often held at Allou, which also provides relaxing moments for all the family at the
        restaurants and cafes on the location.</string>
    <string name="telephone_kid_alloufunpark">+30 21 0809 2888</string>
    <string name="url_kid_alloufunpark">www.allou.gr/</string>
    <string name="coordinates_kid_alloufunpark">37.973086, 23.672362</string>
    <string name="advice_kid_alloufunpark">Since Allou! is an outdoor facility, check the weather
        before visiting</string>

    <string name="name_kid_atticazoo">Attica Zoological Park</string>
    <string name="address_kid_atticazoo">Spata, 190 04</string>
    <string name="description_kid_atticazoo">Attica Zoological Park in the area of Spata is a
        private zoo covering an area of approximately 20 hectares which is home to more than 2000
        animals from 400 different species. Over the years it now includes a number of themed
        sections with birds, mammals, marine mammals and reptiles from all over the world. The Park
        is an excellent destination for education and entertainment for families and animal lovers,
        who can see the lions, giraffes, monkeys, tigers, bears, penguins and many more while
        walking through the zoo. Fascinating information about their habits and lives is learned
        while admiring the animals. The Park also has a cafeteria, a souvenir shop, picnic areas
        and a playground.</string>
    <string name="telephone_kid_atticazoo">+30 21 0663 4724</string>
    <string name="url_kid_atticazoo">www.atticapark.com/</string>
    <string name="coordinates_kid_atticazoo">37.979465, 23.911273</string>
    <string name="advice_kid_atticazoo">If you want to combine your visit with shopping, there is
        shopping village right next door</string>

    <string name="name_kid_planetarium">Eugenides Foundation Planetarium</string>
    <string name="address_kid_planetarium">Leoforos Andrea Syngrou 387, Palaio Faliro, 175 64</string>
    <string name="description_kid_planetarium">The Planetarium is the ideal place to take your toddlers if
        you would like them to gain an understanding of complex concepts in a fun and effective way.
        Through performances and interactive games, children (and adults) feel closer to the world
        of science – which many see as distant and unknown – and develop a greater comprehension of
        it. There are digital shows for young children such as The Little Prince, and also for
        teenagers and adults such as Space Travel. For the older children there is an Interactive
        Science and Technology Exhibition which aims to introduce them to new concepts (materials,
        audio and video communication, principles of biotechnology). Children are also given the
        chance to observe the applications of science and technology in everyday life, such as  how
        animated movies are produced.</string>
    <string name="telephone_kid_planetarium">+30 21 0946 9600</string>
    <string name="url_kid_planetarium">www.eugenfound.edu.gr</string>
    <string name="coordinates_kid_planetarium">37.939816, 23.696333</string>
    <string name="advice_kid_planetarium">Screenings on workdays at 17:30 till 20:30, 10:30 till 14:30
        on weekends </string>

    <string name="name_kid_pnyka">Pnyka and Filopappou hills</string>
    <string name="address_kid_pnyka">Athens, 117 41</string>
    <string name="description_kid_pnyka">Pnyka and Filopappou hills, which are located right next to
    the Acropolis, are an oasis in the middle of Athens. The scenery is beautiful and you can enjoy
    a picnic with the family right in the city center.</string>
    <string name="telephone_kid_pnyka"></string>
    <string name="url_kid_pnyka"></string>
    <string name="coordinates_kid_pnyka">37.971541, 23.719188</string>
    <string name="advice_kid_pnyka">From Pnyka hill you have the most gorgeous view of the Acropolis.
    Don\'t miss the photo op.</string>

    <string name="name_kid_goulandri">Goulandris museum of natural history</string>
    <string name="address_kid_goulandri">Levidou 13, Kifissia, 145 62</string>
    <string name="description_kid_goulandri">Goulandris Museum of Natural History is a magical place
        for children. Visitors can admire the rich collection of life-sized animal replicas. One
        thing is certain … children of all ages will hold their breath while older visitors will
        find the museum really educational. A visit to the Goulandris Museum of Natural History is a
        great opportunity for children to come into contact with the animal and plant kingdoms and
        understand the interaction of ecosystems. Children will be impressed by the life sized
        exhibits, which even include mammals. The exhibition at the Gaia Centre aims to provide
        information about the way our planet works and mankind’s influence on it. Its ultimate goal
        is to educate visitors about our planet’s resources and improve visitors’ ecological
        consciousness.</string>
    <string name="telephone_kid_goulandri">+30 21 0801 5870</string>
    <string name="url_kid_goulandri">www.gnhm.gr/en/</string>
    <string name="coordinates_kid_goulandri">38.074484, 23.814837</string>
    <string name="advice_kid_goulandri">Don\'t miss the beautiful cafe-restaurant of the museum</string>

    <string name="loofie_says">Loofie Says:</string>
    <string name="ImageView_content_description">Main image</string>
</resources>
